<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" translatedname="English" nowhitespace="false">

    <eventtext.youmujoin.c1>Europa, as noisy and restless as ever — bustling stations, moving crowds, and that damned headache again... you think to yourself as you pass through the station’s airlock.\n\nBut as you climb the ladder and step inside, a strange sense of dissonance draws your attention.\n\nIts source is a young girl seemingly resting with her eyes closed — she looks to be in her teens, her refined features outshining even the Europa Alliance’s most exaggerated propaganda of their leaders. Her silver-white hair reminds you oddly of light reflected off a sunken ship’s porthole. Shaking off that unlucky thought, you notice the two empty sheaths hanging at her waist.\n\nYou can’t help but wonder — who exactly is this girl, so out of place here?</eventtext.youmujoin.c1>
    <eventtext.youmujoin.o1>Take a closer look.</eventtext.youmujoin.o1>

    <eventtext.youmujoin.c2>You’re about to approach, but the seemingly unguarded girl lifts her head first.\n\nIn that instant, you feel as though a blade were being drawn — not like the boarding axes of the Alliance’s security officers, nor the ornate ceremonial swords of assistants, but something purer: a weapon forged from the very essence of cold oceans, tempered through countless ages, far beyond what mortals could wield. Neither blood nor spirits would dare leave a mark upon such a perfect edge.\n\nFor a fleeting moment, you’re certain — before you could even realize it, she could have cleaved you, and the entire station, in two… even though both of her sheaths are empty.\n\n“Excuse me, do you have any watermelon?” The girl’s voice is just as you imagined — clear and crisp, with a metallic ring, like a flash of swordlight scattering cherry blossoms. …Wait, watermelon?</eventtext.youmujoin.c2>
    <eventtext.youmujoin.o2>“Watermelon?”</eventtext.youmujoin.o2>

    <eventtext.youmujoin.c3>“Yes, the round fruit with green rind and black stripes... could you help me find one?” she asks, a bit embarrassed.\n\nOnly now do you realize — this girl seems far more approachable than you expected.</eventtext.youmujoin.c3>
    <eventtext.youmujoin.o3>Check if you have what she’s looking for.</eventtext.youmujoin.o3>

    <eventtext.youmujoin.c3.c1>It just so happens you’re carrying a watermelon. The girl looks delighted — but soon frowns, as if troubled about how to speak.\n\n“Well, you see, I got lost while chasing a rabbit… and now I have no idea where I am. Could you give me a ride?”</eventtext.youmujoin.c3.c1>
    <eventtext.youmujoin.c3.o1>“It would be my honor, Miss Youmu Konpaku.”</eventtext.youmujoin.c3.o1>
    <eventtext.youmujoin.c3.o1.c1>The girl breathes a small sigh of relief. “Thank you!” she says, then runs toward your submarine. Wait a second… did she ever tell you her name?</eventtext.youmujoin.c3.o1.c1>

    <eventtext.youmujoin.c3.o2>“Sorry, but we’re already full.”</eventtext.youmujoin.c3.o2>
    <eventtext.youmujoin.c3.o2.c1>You were planning to brush her off — but come on, it’s Youmu! How could anyone possibly refuse her?</eventtext.youmujoin.c3.o2.c1>

    <eventtext.youmujoin.c3.c2>After rummaging around, it seems you don’t have a watermelon. You look up — the girl is quietly waiting for your reply.</eventtext.youmujoin.c3.c2>
    <eventtext.youmujoin.c3.c2.o1>“Sorry, I don’t think I have what you’re looking for. But I can try to find one...”</eventtext.youmujoin.c3.c2.o1>
    <eventtext.youmujoin.c3.c2.c1>The girl lets out a small sigh and ignores you. “What am I going to do... Lady Yuyuko will…” you hear her muttering as you leave. Speaking of watermelons, maybe the station’s vending machine has some?</eventtext.youmujoin.c3.c2.c1>

    <eventtext.youmujoin_return.c1>Guided by that same strange aura around her, you easily find the girl again within the station.</eventtext.youmujoin_return.c1>
    <eventtext.youmujoin_return.o1>“Hey, I got the watermelon you asked for...”</eventtext.youmujoin_return.o1>
    <eventtext.youmujoin_return.o1.c2>You were about to say that — but then remember, you actually don’t have any watermelon with you.</eventtext.youmujoin_return.o1.c2>
    <eventtext.youmujoin_return.o2>Leave her be.</eventtext.youmujoin_return.o2>

    <eventtext.youmujoin.c3.c2.o2>“Sorry, I don’t think I have what you want. Let’s just go our separate ways.”</eventtext.youmujoin.c3.c2.o2>


    <!--Aya Joining Event Text-->
    <EventText.aya_join.c1>Another successful deep dive. After leaving the submarine, you decided to take a good rest at this outpost. However, as you walked through the narrow corridors, you suddenly realized that this place, like your submarine cabin, was suffocatingly cramped. The steel walls enclosing the tiny space represented nearly all that the residents of Europa had ever seen since birth. Though books contained many descriptions of the surface world, how many have truly seen it? The darkness of the deep sea devours all imagination of freedom.</EventText.aya_join.c1>
    <EventText.aya_join.o1>Continue</EventText.aya_join.o1>
    <EventText.aya_join.c2>But these are just thoughts. You still have much work to do: inventory, arranging tasks, and coordinating with the station governors. Your personal rest time can only be squeezed into the gaps between these duties.</EventText.aya_join.c2>
    <EventText.aya_join.o2>Continue</EventText.aya_join.o2>
    <EventText.aya_join.c3>"Hello? Do you have a moment?" A female voice suddenly spoke behind you, and you felt a light tap on your shoulder.</EventText.aya_join.c3>
    <EventText.aya_join.o3>Turn around</EventText.aya_join.o3>
    <EventText.aya_join.c4>A black-haired, seemingly beautiful girl stood behind you, holding a notebook and pen. She looked like a journalist, but something behind her caught your attention—a pair of black wings, strikingly similar to bird wings described in books.</EventText.aya_join.c4>
    <EventText.aya_join.o4>Continue</EventText.aya_join.o4>
    <EventText.aya_join.c5>But the girl didn’t give you a chance to ask about the wings. Seeing you nod, she immediately launched a barrage of questions about deep-sea navigation.</EventText.aya_join.c5>
    <EventText.aya_join.o5>Answer her</EventText.aya_join.o5>
    <EventText.aya_join.o6>Refuse to answer</EventText.aya_join.o6>
    <EventText.aya_join.c6>"Good grief, are people here all this cold…" Seeing that you had no intention of answering her questions, the girl shook her head and walked away.</EventText.aya_join.c6>
    <EventText.aya_join.o7>Forget this encounter and continue enjoying your hard-earned free time.</EventText.aya_join.o7>
    <EventText.aya_join.c7>"Ahahaha, thank you for your cooperation." After answering her questions one by one, she carefully recorded your answers in her notebook, then smiled at you: "People here are so cold, you’re the first willing to answer me. You seem to be a submarine captain, right?"</EventText.aya_join.c7>
    <EventText.aya_join.o8>"Yes, that over there is my submarine."</EventText.aya_join.o8>
    <EventText.aya_join.o9>"No, I just know a bit about these things."</EventText.aya_join.o9>
    <EventText.aya_join.c8>The girl looked slightly disappointed upon hearing you. "Ahahaha… thank you for your cooperation, I’ll come find you again when I get the chance," she said, then left.</EventText.aya_join.c8>
    <EventText.aya_join.c9>You encounter the winged girl again. Seeing you approach, she said, "I remember you… what brings you here?"</EventText.aya_join.c9>
    <EventText.aya_join.o10>"I thought about it, and answering your questions is fine. Ask away."</EventText.aya_join.o10>
    <EventText.aya_join.o11>"Nothing, just passing by."</EventText.aya_join.o11>
    <EventText.aya_join.c10>"Ahaha, my intuition was right." The girl smiled, then said: "I am Aya Shameimaru, an upright and incorruptible journalist! I’m currently looking for a big scoop and maybe to find my friend. Your ship seems interesting—can I come with you?"</EventText.aya_join.c10>
    <EventText.aya_join.o12>"Wait, did you say your name is Aya Shameimaru?"</EventText.aya_join.o12>
    <EventText.aya_join.c11>"Yes? Have you read my paper?" She seemed pleasantly surprised that you knew her name.</EventText.aya_join.c11>
    <EventText.aya_join.o13>"No… I just remembered, one of my crew keeps talking about giving you a lesson."</EventText.aya_join.o13>
    <EventText.aya_join.c12>"Huh? A lesson?" Aya’s expression froze as she frowned, pondering who she might have offended here.</EventText.aya_join.c12>
    <EventText.aya_join.c13>Finally, her expression changed, and she anxiously asked, "That crew member—is it a white wolf tengu named Momiji Inubashiri?"</EventText.aya_join.c13>
    <EventText.aya_join.o14>"You guessed right. At a previous outpost, I found her without her ID and pocket money, so I helped her replace her documents and accompanied her to find her companions."</EventText.aya_join.o14>
    <EventText.aya_join.c14>Aya’s expression was lively. After a moment, she said: "Um… Captain, could you do me a favor?" She tried to calm down, but her trembling hands revealed her inner turmoil.</EventText.aya_join.c14>
    <EventText.aya_join.c15>"Help me buy some gifts… here’s the list, don’t look! Just give the list to the merchant and they’ll know what to do…" She shoved a small note into your hand, saying: "Save me, or Momiji will eat me alive!"</EventText.aya_join.c15>
    <EventText.aya_join.o15>Take the list</EventText.aya_join.o15>
    <EventText.aya_join.o16>"Big scoop…? Well, we’re short-handed, so it’s fine if you come along. But what about your wings?"</EventText.aya_join.o16>
    <EventText.aya_join.o17>"Ma’am, it’s too dangerous for a journalist on a submarine. I’m afraid I can’t agree."</EventText.aya_join.o17>
    <EventText.aya_join.c16>You found the girl again, and she recognized you. "What’s up? Any discoveries?" she asked excitedly.</EventText.aya_join.c16>
    <EventText.aya_join.o18>"Actually, I have a submarine. Do you need something?"</EventText.aya_join.o18>
    <EventText.aya_join.o19>"No, I’m just passing by."</EventText.aya_join.o19>
    <EventText.aya_join.c17>"You mean this?" Aya flapped her wings and said: "I’m a tengu… never mind, you wouldn’t understand, it won’t interfere with anything anyway." She seemed excited as she walked toward your submarine. Watching her back, you felt an unfamiliar aura in the deep sea.</EventText.aya_join.c17>
    <EventText.aya_join.o20>You subconsciously thought for a moment and found an answer in the corner of your memory—</EventText.aya_join.o20>
    <EventText.aya_join.c18>"She looks so free… future voyages might be more interesting."</EventText.aya_join.c18>
    <EventText.aya_join.c19>You encountered Aya Shameimaru again, and she recognized you. Seeing you approach, she waved and asked: "So? Can I board your submarine now?"</EventText.aya_join.c19>
    <EventText.aya_join.o21>"Of course, we’re short-handed. But what about your wings?"</EventText.aya_join.o21>
    <EventText.aya_join.o22>"No, I’m just passing by."</EventText.aya_join.o22>
    <EventText.aya_join.c20>"Ah! Thank you so much! I’ll go find Momiji now, see you!" The girl said this and hurried away.</EventText.aya_join.c20>
    <EventText.aya_join.o23>"Looks like future voyages will be a lot more interesting."</EventText.aya_join.o23>
    <EventText.aya_join.c21>Aya Shameimaru joins the crew</EventText.aya_join.c21>
    <EventText.aya_join.c22>"Just give the list to the merchant, my fate is in your hands!"</EventText.aya_join.c22>


    <!--Mokou Joining Event Text-->
    <EventText.mokou_join.c1>After finishing a dive and successfully completing a dangerous voyage, the other crew members take their distributed rewards to enjoy the aftermath. After all, every dive is a life-or-death adventure, and a crew like yours sees hundreds of people silently vanish in various corners of Europa every day. People always die, so one must seize the moments of safety to indulge in life.
        But they can enjoy it; you cannot. As the captain, you have to negotiate with the station governor, call the engineers from the station’s engineering department to repair the hull, and replenish weapons, ammunition, and other essentials. All of this requires your attention.</EventText.mokou_join.c1>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o1>Continue</EventText.mokou_join.o1>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c2>Walking through the long, monotonous corridors of the station, a splash of red and white, almost incongruous with the surroundings, caught your eye. You were instinctively drawn to the figure and soon made out the details. It was a capable woman with a masculine aura, white long hair decorated with several bows, wearing red overalls covered with talismans you couldn't understand, and a white shirt underneath.</EventText.mokou_join.c2>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o2>Continue</EventText.mokou_join.o2>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c3>She seemed to radiate a burning energy; even a casual glance made you feel the surge of vitality. Yet, despite her incongruity with the dark, cramped submarine corridors, she appeared troubled, leaning against the wall with her arms crossed and frowning. It seemed she had a problem—should you ask about it?</EventText.mokou_join.c3>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o3>Go check on her.</EventText.mokou_join.o3>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o4>Not my concern.</EventText.mokou_join.o4>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c4>You didn’t have much free time to help everyone in trouble along the way; you had your own duties to attend to.</EventText.mokou_join.c4>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o5>Thinking this, you walked away.</EventText.mokou_join.o5>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c5>As you approached her, you felt the intense, almost tangible heat emanating from her grow stronger with every step. Only when you stood beside her and asked did the sensation suddenly subside.</EventText.mokou_join.c5>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o6>"Hello, miss, are you in some kind of trouble?"</EventText.mokou_join.o6>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c6>"…" She seemed surprised by your sudden approach but answered honestly: "My ship left me behind, that bastard… when he found me, he said… and now he hasn’t returned for so long."</EventText.mokou_join.c6>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o7>Continue</EventText.mokou_join.o7>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c7>After a few complaints, she asked: "So, why are you looking for me?"</EventText.mokou_join.c7>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o8>"You were left behind by your ship? Are you a sailor too?"</EventText.mokou_join.o8>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c8>"Yes, I used to handle the mechanical and electrical maintenance on board," she replied frankly, then looked at you and asked: "What do you want?"</EventText.mokou_join.c8>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o9>"Well… do you need a ship to take you along? Actually, I’m a captain too."</EventText.mokou_join.o9>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c9>"Take me along?" She scrutinized you from head to toe. You quickly showed your ID to prove your words, but she barely glanced at it, muttering to herself as if recalling something amusing:</EventText.mokou_join.c9>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o10>Continue</EventText.mokou_join.o10>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c10>"Hmph, Kaguya, you bastard, when you came to find me back then you left me behind. Let’s see what happens now that I’m on another ship."</EventText.mokou_join.c10>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o11>Continue</EventText.mokou_join.o11>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c11>You didn’t understand what she said, but the oppressive aura she initially radiated suddenly dissipated. She extended her hand to you:
        "Alright, you can call me Fujiwara no Mokou, the immortal phoenix of Hourai. Where’s our ship? Let’s set off."</EventText.mokou_join.c11>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o12>"Alright, looking forward to working with you, Miss Fujiwara."</EventText.mokou_join.o12>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c12>Fujiwara no Mokou has joined the crew</EventText.mokou_join.c12>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o13>"Ah, in that case, I can’t really help much, sorry."</EventText.mokou_join.o13>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c13>You apologized for not being able to help her and then left.</EventText.mokou_join.c13>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c14>After leaving the cabin, you stretched. One problem solved, though many more remained. At least the upcoming voyage now had a bit more assurance.
        At that moment, you saw the white-haired woman again. She wandered aimlessly in the corridor, still looking somewhat troubled, but honestly it didn’t seem urgent.</EventText.mokou_join.c14>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c15>You encountered the white-haired woman again.</EventText.mokou_join.c15>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o14>Talk to her</EventText.mokou_join.o14>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c16>You approached and greeted her. She seemed surprised you came back, asking with a hint of caution: "Hello… what brings you here?"</EventText.mokou_join.c16>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o15>Continue</EventText.mokou_join.o15>
    <EventText.mokou_join.c17>You notice a spark flicker in her hand—was it an illusion?</EventText.mokou_join.c17>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o16>"Actually, if you don’t want to just wait here, I can take you along. I’m a captain too."</EventText.mokou_join.o16>
    <EventText.mokou_join.o17>Ignore her</EventText.mokou_join.o17>

    <!--Patchouli Joining Event Text-->
    <EventText.patchouli_join.c1>Among the crowd, you noticed a familiar yet strange figure wandering in a corner. You had seen a similar face on some TV programs. She was once famous on Europa for her numerous discoveries and inventions, but in recent months, news of her had been scarce. You had assumed she had voluntarily withdrawn from the spotlight due to factional struggles, but today, you unexpectedly encountered her here.
        Your curiosity was piqued, and you decided to approach her.</EventText.patchouli_join.c1>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.o1>"Excuse me, are you Dr. Patchouli?"</EventText.patchouli_join.o1>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.c2>"Yes, that’s me. And you are…" She looked up at you with her large eyes, slightly shadowed, appearing somewhat fatigued.</EventText.patchouli_join.c2>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.o2>"I’m the newly arrived captain," you said seriously. "I’ve heard of your achievements, but your sudden disappearance a while ago worried everyone. I’d like to know what happened."</EventText.patchouli_join.o2>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.c3>She didn’t seem annoyed by your interruption, and even cast a different kind of glance at you. "Hmm… it was all public plans. They knew I had some experience making rockets, so they asked me to build another one. For Remilia’s sake, I didn’t refuse."</EventText.patchouli_join.c3>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.o3>"Then why did you suddenly disappear for such a long time? Was the work too exhausting? Building a rocket doesn’t sound easy." You had heard about the rocket program—an effort by the people of Europa to return to Earth—but after Patchouli’s disappearance, no new information had emerged.</EventText.patchouli_join.o3>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.c4>"That matter…" The girl coughed lightly twice, "Could you help me get some asthma medicine? I don’t have much left."</EventText.patchouli_join.c4>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.o4>"Medicine?" You thought for a moment and recalled the asthma medication. "Would Budesonide work?"</EventText.patchouli_join.o4>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.c5>"Thank you." The girl accepted the medicine and expressed her gratitude.</EventText.patchouli_join.c5>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.o5>Here is the medicine she needs. "Dr. Patchouli, could you tell me what happens next?"</EventText.patchouli_join.o5>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.c6>"The continuation of the rocket project… let’s talk on your submarine. I need a place to rest," she said with a meaningful glance. "Remilia said she has already seen today’s fate."</EventText.patchouli_join.c6>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.o6>Here is the medicine she needs. "Dr. Patchouli, are you alright?"</EventText.patchouli_join.o6>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.c7>"Thank you for your concern. May I rest on your submarine for a while?" she said, glancing at you meaningfully. "Remilia said she has already seen today’s fate."</EventText.patchouli_join.c7>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.c8>You don’t have any Budesonide on hand—perhaps you can buy a bottle from a merchant?</EventText.patchouli_join.c8>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.o7>"Please wait a moment, miss. I think I can get some now."</EventText.patchouli_join.o7>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.c9>You hurried off, hoping you had enough Marks on you.</EventText.patchouli_join.c9>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.c10>You found the purple-haired girl again; her long purple hair made her stand out in the crowd.</EventText.patchouli_join.c10>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.o8>"Dr. Patchouli, we meet again."</EventText.patchouli_join.o8>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.c11>"But you didn’t manage to find the medicine she needed. You’ll have to check elsewhere."</EventText.patchouli_join.c11>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.o9>Just passing by.</EventText.patchouli_join.o9>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.o10>Just passing by.</EventText.patchouli_join.o10>
    <EventText.patchouli_join.c12>Your memory of this medicine is vague; perhaps you can check with a pharmaceutical vendor?</EventText.patchouli_join.c12>

    <!--Yuka Joining Event Text-->
    <EventText.yuka_join.c1>Not every captain is fortunate enough to see flowers—that’s a luxury from distant Earth, belonging to the land-dwellers. Fortunately, you still have pictures to look at; the words in those albums once stirred your childhood imagination.
        But now you actually see a flower—not the bizarre, flower-like alien creatures of the deep sea, but a real flower from Earth you had seen in the albums. You remember it being called a sunflower. In any case, why is it here? In the hands of that green-haired girl?</EventText.yuka_join.c1>
    <EventText.yuka_join.o1>Walk up and greet her.</EventText.yuka_join.o1>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c2>As you stepped closer, the girl’s eyes swept toward you. For a moment, it felt as if some terrifying force had fixed its gaze on you. But the feeling lasted only briefly; then she turned her head back as if she hadn’t noticed you, continuing to tend to the blooming sunflower in her hands.</EventText.yuka_join.c2>
    <EventText.yuka_join.o2>"Hello?"</EventText.yuka_join.o2>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c3>"A human?" She tilted her head in surprise upon hearing your greeting, as if wondering why you approached her.</EventText.yuka_join.c3>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c4>But the surprise lasted only a moment; you saw the corners of her mouth lift in a gentle arc, and she smiled at you appropriately, saying, "Hello."</EventText.yuka_join.c4>
    <EventText.yuka_join.o3>Curiously ask about the sunflower.</EventText.yuka_join.o3>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c5>"You mean the flower?" She glanced down at the bright blossom in her hands.</EventText.yuka_join.c5>
    <EventText.yuka_join.o4>Continue</EventText.yuka_join.o4>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c6>"Flowers are indeed rare here… I heard that the kappa cultivated some unusual flowers here, so I came to have a look. But…" She seemed a bit troubled as she looked at you.</EventText.yuka_join.c6>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c7>"Transportation here is inconvenient. If I try to swim from the sea directly, the seeds I brought will not survive the salt… What should I do?"</EventText.yuka_join.c7>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c8>Swim… from the sea? At thousands of meters below the ocean? You were astonished by her words and her casual attitude. You know that a few years ago many youkai came from Earth to Europa, often possessing great powers, but you had never heard of anyone this capable. You didn’t doubt her words, yet some instinctive sense of danger screamed at you—best to believe her.</EventText.yuka_join.c8>
    <EventText.yuka_join.o5>"Well… actually, I have my own submarine. Would you like to take a ride with me, miss?"</EventText.yuka_join.o5>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c9>"Your ship?" The woman seemed intrigued, her smile widening slightly with a hint of peculiarity. "Can I take that to mean you’re inviting me aboard?" she asked, clearly interested.</EventText.yuka_join.c9>
    <EventText.yuka_join.o6> nod</EventText.yuka_join.o6>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c10>Her expression immediately calmed. You could not read her thoughts, but she nodded, accepting your invitation. "Alright, since you invited me, I’ll leave it in your hands."</EventText.yuka_join.c10>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c11>She handed you the sunflower. You took it and then heard her say, "You can call me Yuka Kazami. Just an ordinary flower youkai. Since I’m ready to board your ship, let’s see if we can find any interesting flowers under the sea together."</EventText.yuka_join.c11>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c12>An ordinary flower youkai wouldn’t dare swim thousands of meters underwater, you thought, secretly amused. Still, you welcome her joining the crew.</EventText.yuka_join.c12>
    <EventText.yuka_join.o7>"It’s truly an honor. I look forward to working with you, Miss Kazami."</EventText.yuka_join.o7>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c13>Yuka Kazami has joined the crew.</EventText.yuka_join.c13>
    <EventText.yuka_join.o8>"It’s truly an honor. I look forward to working with you, Miss Kazami."</EventText.yuka_join.o8>
    <EventText.yuka_join.o9>She seems scary; better keep your distance.</EventText.yuka_join.o9>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c14>Thinking so, you hurriedly left.</EventText.yuka_join.c14>
    <EventText.yuka_join.o10>She seems scary; better keep your distance.</EventText.yuka_join.o10>
    <EventText.yuka_join.o11>Ignore her; it’s not important.</EventText.yuka_join.o11>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c15>The sunflower shines too brightly in this deep, dim station. You see it and the woman again.</EventText.yuka_join.c15>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c16>Your heart trembles, and you instinctively step away from her. Yet when you see her again, you can’t help but look a few more times, wondering whether to approach and talk.</EventText.yuka_join.c16>
    <EventText.yuka_join.c17>You muster your courage.</EventText.yuka_join.c17>

    <!--Tenshi Joining Event Text-->
    <EventText.tenshi_join.c1>For the people of Europa, the concept of “sky” is unimaginably distant. The blue canopy described in the enlightening books and by the first pioneers who came here was, in your understanding, nothing more than light filtering through clouds—a mere illusion, not worth seeing.</EventText.tenshi_join.c1>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.o1>Continue.</EventText.tenshi_join.o1>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.c2>However, you never imagined that you could actually see someone here in this dim, cramped station who immediately evokes this concept you’ve never witnessed firsthand.</EventText.tenshi_join.c2>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.o2>Blue hair… are these some of the foreign youkai?</EventText.tenshi_join.o2>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.c3>Not far from you is a blue-haired girl. The fabric of her clothing is clearly no ordinary material, making her seem like the daughter of some noble family.</EventText.tenshi_join.c3>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.c4>Yet she looks troubled about something.</EventText.tenshi_join.c4>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.o3>"You seem to be having some trouble. Can I help you with anything?"</EventText.tenshi_join.o3>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.c5>"Trouble?" The girl seemed a bit relieved, then complained: "The security here is terrible! I just arrived and a group of people stole my hat."</EventText.tenshi_join.c5>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.o4>"Your hat was stolen?"</EventText.tenshi_join.o4>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.c6>"Yes, it’s just a hat, but peaches are scarce here, so I’d really like to get it back." She said this, then asked, "So, would you help me retrieve my hat?"</EventText.tenshi_join.c6>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.o5>You’re not entirely sure why the hat is connected to peaches, but since she asked, and it’s just a small favor, you agree to help.</EventText.tenshi_join.o5>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.c7>"A black one, with a peach on top. Good luck, I’m counting on you."</EventText.tenshi_join.c7>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.c9>"Ah, thank you so much!" The girl said excitedly, then plucked the peach off the hat and offered it to you. "This is a peach from the Celestial Realm, really delicious. Would you like one?"</EventText.tenshi_join.c9>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.c10>You notice that a new peach quickly grows back on the hat, and only then do you understand why Tenshi had linked the hat with a peach in the first place.</EventText.tenshi_join.c10>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.o7>"Thanks for the peach, but I spent quite a bit to get this hat; one peach probably isn’t enough, right?"</EventText.tenshi_join.o7>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.c11>Your words leave the girl a bit puzzled. "Is that so? But I don’t have any money on me…" She plucks another peach, munching thoughtfully, then suddenly says, "Then how about I help you too? I’m Byakuren Tenshi, a Celestial Being!"</EventText.tenshi_join.c11>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.o8>"A Celestial Being?"</EventText.tenshi_join.o8>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.c12>"Someone who’s achieved enlightenment. Anyway, I look forward to working with you in the future!" She said cheerfully.</EventText.tenshi_join.c12>
    <EventText.tenshi_join.c13>"Ah? Haven’t found it yet? Just a black hat, with a peach on top, very conspicuous."</EventText.tenshi_join.c13>

    <!--Momiji Joining Event Text-->
    <EventText.momizi_join.c1>The white-haired tengu girl has been pacing around for a long time; you notice she seems to be looking for someone. She has already asked many passersby, but it looks like she hasn’t had any luck.</EventText.momizi_join.c1>
    <EventText.momizi_join.o1>Go take a look</EventText.momizi_join.o1>
    <EventText.momizi_join.c2>Seeing you approach, she comes forward and speaks to you first.</EventText.momizi_join.c2>
    <EventText.momizi_join.c3>"Have you seen a crow-tengu dressed like a reporter?" she asks anxiously. "She’s my companion—we got separated after yesterday’s incident."</EventText.momizi_join.c3>
    <EventText.momizi_join.o2>"A crow-tengu reporter? Do you mean Aya Shameimaru?"</EventText.momizi_join.o2>
    <EventText.momizi_join.c4>"Eh! You know her?" The tengu girl looks pleasantly surprised. "Where is she?"</EventText.momizi_join.c4>
    <EventText.momizi_join.o3>"She’s on my ship. I’m a submarine captain. She said she’d join my crew to follow the sub and look for stories."</EventText.momizi_join.o3>
    <EventText.momizi_join.c5>"That’s too much!" The tengu girl seems angry upon hearing this. "After the outpost fell they left me here. My ID and spending money were on her! If not for the kappa helping me, I would have starved!"</EventText.momizi_join.c5>
    <EventText.momizi_join.o4>"Ha... haha..."</EventText.momizi_join.o4>
    <EventText.momizi_join.c6>"Well, since she’s on your ship, then I’ll come along too!" the tengu girl says. "My name is Momiji Inubashiri, a white-wolf tengu—pleased to meet you!"</EventText.momizi_join.c6>
    <EventText.momizi_join.o5>You smile and shake her hand, welcoming her aboard.</EventText.momizi_join.o5>
    <EventText.momizi_join.o6>"Crow-tengu? I’m not familiar with them."</EventText.momizi_join.o6>
    <EventText.momizi_join.c7>Your remark seems to disappoint her a little, but she says, "Then excuse me," and moves on to ask others.</EventText.momizi_join.c7>
    <EventText.momizi_join.o7>Ignore her</EventText.momizi_join.o7>
    <EventText.momizi_join.c8>Better not get involved.</EventText.momizi_join.c8>
    <EventText.momizi_join.c9>You see the white-haired tengu again; she still hasn’t resolved the situation.</EventText.momizi_join.c9>
    <EventText.momizi_join.c10>"Hello, is there something you need?" She seems a bit surprised by your return.</EventText.momizi_join.c10>
    <EventText.momizi_join.o8>"I recall—you’re looking for someone, right?"</EventText.momizi_join.o8>
    <EventText.momizi_join.c11>"Yes." She nods, then continues: "A crow-tengu with a camera, named Aya Shameimaru. Do you have any leads?"</EventText.momizi_join.c11>
    <EventText.momizi_join.o9>"Sorry, I don’t know where she is. But I don’t think she’s in this outpost."</EventText.momizi_join.o9>
    <EventText.momizi_join.c12>"Oh... is that so..." She looks clearly disappointed. "But I can’t go to other outposts—my ID is with my companion, and I have no money to replace it..."</EventText.momizi_join.c12>
    <EventText.momizi_join.o10>"If you like, I can arrange a replacement ID for you. I also have a submarine—you could come with me to look for her."</EventText.momizi_join.o10>
    <EventText.momizi_join.c13>"Really!" She looks delighted. "Thank you so much! My name is Momiji Inubashiri—please take care of me!"</EventText.momizi_join.c13>
    <EventText.momizi_join.c14>"Ah! Thank you!" Momiji exclaims happily when she sees the ID in your hand. "From now on, the white-wolf tengu Momiji Inubashiri is at your service!"</EventText.momizi_join.c14>
    <EventText.momizi_join.c15>"Did the ID paperwork run into trouble? Sorry for the hassle." She looks embarrassed but grateful. "I’ll be relying on you!"</EventText.momizi_join.c15>

    <!--Momiji ID Replacement Event Text-->
    <EventText.momizi_idcard_event.c1>"Is this the white-wolf tengu named Momiji Inubashiri?" He glances at you and stamps the permit in hand.</EventText.momizi_idcard_event.c1>
    <EventText.momizi_idcard_event.o1>Replace ID — 50 Marks</EventText.momizi_idcard_event.o1>
    <EventText.momizi_idcard_event.c2>"These youkai are troublesome one by one. If you want her onboard, make sure you keep an eye on her."</EventText.momizi_idcard_event.c2>
    <EventText.momizi_idcard_event.c3>You check your pockets and find you don’t have enough money—maybe you can sell some unused materials?</EventText.momizi_idcard_event.c3>
    <EventText.momizi_idcard_event.o2>Think it over</EventText.momizi_idcard_event.o2>

    <!--Aya's Gift List Event Text-->
    <EventText.aya_gift_list_event.c1>"Hmm... these requests are uncommon..." The merchant eyes the list oddly, then fetches a gift box from the warehouse.</EventText.aya_gift_list_event.c1>
    <EventText.aya_gift_list_event.c2>"That’ll be 200 Marks. Also, please settle Miss Aya Shameimaru’s outstanding 300 Marks debt." </EventText.aya_gift_list_event.c2>
    <EventText.aya_gift_list_event.c1.o1>Pay 300 Marks</EventText.aya_gift_list_event.c1.o1>
    <EventText.aya_gift_list_event.c3>You check your pockets and realize you don’t have enough money—perhaps you can sell some unused materials?</EventText.aya_gift_list_event.c3>
    <EventText.aya_gift_list_event.o2>Think it over</EventText.aya_gift_list_event.o2>

    <!--Akyuu Recruitment Event Text-->
    <EventText.akyuu_join.c1>You’ve run into her again, and she clearly recognizes you as well. “So, what do you say? May I join you on your submarine adventure this time?” She looks at you expectantly, waiting for your answer.</EventText.akyuu_join.c1>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.o1>“Of course! Welcome aboard!”</EventText.akyuu_join.o1>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.c2>“Thank you so much! Ah, I haven’t even introduced myself yet... My name is Hieda no Akyuu, just a humble chronicler of history. Well then, I’ll go ahead and get familiar with our ship. See you soon.” You watch as the girl jogs toward your submarine — and you know you’ll never forget her name.</EventText.akyuu_join.c2>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.o2>“It’s quite dangerous aboard the submarine… I’m afraid I can’t allow it.”</EventText.akyuu_join.o2>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.c3>“I see... That’s a shame. I’m sorry for troubling you, then. But if you ever change your mind, please come find me again.” Her spirits fall immediately. You watch her walk away, and faintly hear her murmur, “I really wanted to record so much more…”</EventText.akyuu_join.c3>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.c4>After docking your submarine and entering the outpost, you go over your ship’s supplies in your head — deciding what needs restocking, what to sell, and whether you might use some of those less-than-honest tricks you’re known for.</EventText.akyuu_join.c4>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.o3>Continue</EventText.akyuu_join.o3>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.c5>As always, there’s a lot on your mind when it comes to keeping the vessel running smoothly. Every time you make port, countless tasks crowd your thoughts, noisily competing for attention and draining your already limited energy.</EventText.akyuu_join.c5>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.c6>Just as you’re lamenting that you’re no longer as sharp as you once were, a faint floral fragrance drifts by, cutting through the stale air of the outpost and your submarine — so suddenly pleasant it almost feels unfamiliar.</EventText.akyuu_join.c6>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.c7>When your eyes refocus and the haze lifts, you find the source of the scent — a girl who seems utterly out of place on Europa, with a single flower tucked neatly into her hair.</EventText.akyuu_join.c7>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.o4>Have I seen you somewhere before?</EventText.akyuu_join.o4>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.c8>“Yes, you helped out a lot back at the supply station.” The girl smiles gently. “Is there something I can do for you?”</EventText.akyuu_join.c8>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.o5>My ship’s short on hands. Would you like to lend a hand for a while?</EventText.akyuu_join.o5>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.c9>“Of course! Ah, I haven’t introduced myself yet… My name is Hieda no Akyuu — just a humble recorder of history. Here, please take this as a small token of gratitude.” The girl hands you a small pouch. “Well then, I’ll go ahead and get familiar with our ship. See you soon.” You watch her jog toward your submarine — and know you’ll never forget her name.</EventText.akyuu_join.c9>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.c10>When your eyes refocus and the haze lifts, you find the source of the scent — a girl who seems utterly out of place on Europa, with a single flower tucked neatly into her hair.</EventText.akyuu_join.c10>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.o6>Take a curious look</EventText.akyuu_join.o6>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.c11>As you look toward her, she notices you too. Standing gracefully, she approaches and gives a polite curtsey before speaking: “Pardon me for interrupting, but may I ask — are you part of the crew?”</EventText.akyuu_join.c11>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.o7>Yes, I am. Do you need any help?</EventText.akyuu_join.o7>
    <EventText.akyuu_join.c12>“That’s wonderful!” Her face lights up with joy. “I have a rather bold request — may I join your ship on its journey? I wish to see and record more of this world. Don’t worry, I won’t cause any trouble!”</EventText.akyuu_join.c12>

    <!--Akyuu Mission Event Text-->
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c1>I’ve received several rumors about trade routes. Would you like to take a look?</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c1>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o1>Magical Material Transport</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o1>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c2>The client said... beware of rabbits.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c2>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o2>Accept</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o2>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c3>Safe travels.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c3>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o3>Think it over</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o3>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c4>Too cold today, maybe next time.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c4>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o4>Food Supply Transport</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o4>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c5>Be careful on the way.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c5>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c6>The hungry residents are counting on that food.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c6>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c7>Come back later.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c7>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o5>Furball Cleanup</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o5>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c8>The outer shell of a furball is a valuable material. Remember to collect a few more if you can.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c8>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c9>Have a pleasant journey.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c9>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c10>This kind of simple task is better left to someone else.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c10>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o6>Ghost Line</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o6>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c11>Some say they’ve seen ghostly figures along this route — it might have something to do with the flowers blooming so often nearby.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c11>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c12>May fortune favor you.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c12>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c13>Someone on our crew is… sensitive to ghosts. Maybe next time.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c13>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o7>The Nightmare That Never Wakes</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o7>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c14>A group of unidentified entities is wandering nearby, severely disrupting navigation between stations.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c14>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c15>Stay safe.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c15>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c16>Let’s investigate their true form before heading out.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c16>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o8>Special Commission</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o8>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c17>Rumor has it that groups of multicolored UFOs have been gathering nearby. They’re offering a high reward to anyone who can deal with them. (Once you start the first UFO mission, you cannot accept other tasks until completing the entire UFO questline. It’s recommended to finish all three UFO missions quickly.)</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c17>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c18>The journey will be dangerous. Please be careful. I’ve prepared some medicine for you — I hope it helps.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c18>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c19>Those UFOs still haven’t vanished? Perhaps it’s time to visit Myouren Temple and demand some answers.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c19>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c20>It seems urgent — someone reported seeing green… flying saucers nearby, and is offering a generous bounty for anyone who can resolve the situation. (Once you start the first UFO mission, you cannot accept other tasks until completing the entire UFO questline.)</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c20>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c21>That sounds strange… maybe they just saw wrong.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c21>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o9>Secret Commission (Requires completion of the full UFO questline first)</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o9>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c22>Thanks to your efforts, the Spiritual Orb has been successfully retrieved.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c22>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o10>Submit Proof</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o10>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c23>This is valuable information! As thanks, please accept this. It’s just a replica, but the craftsmanship is so fine you’d hardly tell it from the original.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c23>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c24>It seems you forgot to bring the proof...</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c24>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c25>Due to a previous transport accident, several important items were lost — including an unstable object believed to be a Spiritual Orb. The client is offering a large sum for its discreet recovery.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c25>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c26>This mission must remain confidential. If the Spiritual Orb falls into the wrong hands, the consequences could be severe.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c26>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c27>I can’t fully entrust this matter to you just yet.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c27>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o11>Maybe later</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.o11>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c28>After a long day, I’d rather have a cup of hot tea first.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_mission.c28>

    <!--Event Text: Defeated Green UFO-->
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.c1>I’ve received several rumors about the trade routes. Would you like to take a look?</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.c1>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.o1>Special Commission</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.o1>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.c2>Good news — the green UFOs along the route have disappeared.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.c2>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.o2>“Where else are UFOs still being sighted?”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.o2>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.c3>“I’ve already sent the mission details to your terminal. Please ensure the safety of nearby travelers,” Akyuu says, transferring the task to your terminal. “I’ll be waiting on your ship after your next patrol.”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.c3>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.o3>I’d like to rest for a while first.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.o3>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.c4>You’ve worked hard these past days. Go take a good rest and relax.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.c4>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.c5>“I don’t think you’re quite ready yet...”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.c5>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.o4>Unclear Truth – Loyal Green UFO</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.o4>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.c6>“This log records your battle data. If you wish to recall or practice, feel free to review it.”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.c6>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.o5>Take the log</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.o5>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.o6>Maybe later</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.o6>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.c7>After a long day, I could really use a cup of hot tea first.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission01.c7>

    <!--Event Text: Defeated Red UFO-->
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.c1>I’ve received several rumors about the trade routes. Would you like to take a look?</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.c1>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.o1>Unclear Truth – Furious Red UFO</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.o1>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.c2>“This log records your battle data. If you wish to recall and practice, feel free to review it.”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.c2>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.o2>Take the log</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.o2>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.o3>Maybe later</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.o3>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.c3>After a long day, I could really use a cup of hot tea first.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.c3>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.o4>Special Commission</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.o4>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.c4>“Thank you for your hard work. Thanks to your efforts, those red UFOs have finally disappeared.”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.c4>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.o5>“Where else are UFOs still being sighted?”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.o5>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.c5>“I’ve already sent the mission details to your terminal. The safety of the outpost residents is in your hands,” Akyuu says, transferring the task to your terminal. “I’ll be waiting on your ship after your next patrol.”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.c5>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.o6>I’d like to rest for a while first.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.o6>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.c6>You’ve worked hard these past days. Go take a good rest and relax.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.c6>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.c7>“I don’t think you’re quite ready yet...”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission02.c7>

    <!--Event Text: Defeated Blue UFO-->
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c1>I’ve received several rumors about the trade routes. Would you like to take a look?</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c1>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o1>Unclear Truth – Melancholy Blue UFO</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o1>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c2>“This log records your battle data. If you wish to recall and practice, feel free to review it.”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c2>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o2>Take the log</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o2>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o3>Maybe later</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o3>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c3>After a long day, I could really use a cup of hot tea first.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c3>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o4>Special Commission</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o4>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c4>The girl looks up as you approach, flipping through the log in her hands: “I’ve got good news and bad news.”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c4>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o5>“Let’s hear the good news first—I hope it’s worth it.”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o5>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c5>“Thanks to your efforts, all the previously wandering UFOs have been eliminated.”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c5>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o6>And the bad news?</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o6>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c6>“Now there are even more UFOs along the routes. The ones that had nearly vanished have returned.” The girl looks worried. “Worse still, many claim to have seen strange creatures among them—some say colorful tiger sharks, others giant serpents, and some speak of rainbow-colored UFOs. We need you to investigate the truth behind these sightings.”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c6>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o7>“Let’s head out right now.”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o7>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c7>“This mission might be dangerous. I’ve prepared some medicine for you—please come back safely.” Akyuu sends the mission details to your terminal. “I’ll be waiting on your ship after your next patrol.”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c7>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o8>I’ll think about it first.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o8>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c8>“Alright, please take care of yourself.” The girl seems a little disappointed.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c8>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o9>“Tell me the bad news first—get it over with.”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o9>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o10>“Forget the good news—let’s just deal with the problem now.”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o10>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o11>And the good news?</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o11>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c9>“Thanks to your efforts, all the previously wandering UFOs have been eliminated.” The girl bows slightly to express her gratitude.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c9>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o12>I’d like to rest for a while first.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.o12>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c10>You’ve worked hard these past days. Go take a good rest and relax.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c10>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c11>“I don’t think you’re quite ready yet...”</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission03.c11>

    <!--Event Text: Defeated Nue Houjuu-->
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.c1>The girl looks pleasantly surprised to see you: "You succeeded?"</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.c1>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.o1>"Yes, we found that it was a girl who called herself Nue Houjuu. After waking up, she left on her own."</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.o1>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.c2>"We’ve already received word from Myouren Temple. It seems Nue was under the influence of some kind of wave interference and lost consciousness for a while."</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.c2>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.o2>"Lost consciousness?"</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.o2>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.c3>"Yes, but don’t worry—she’s physically fine, just a bit weak and needs some time to rest." Akyuu flips through the logbook in her hands. "We suspect that this special kind of wave interfered with her mind. We’ll need some time to investigate the cause of the interference."</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.c3>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.o3>"Is there anything I can do to help?"</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.o3>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.c4>"Our preliminary assumption is that something called a ‘Spirit Orb’ disturbed her consciousness. We need to pinpoint its exact location. There have been rumors of strange lights seen in ruins and caves recently. Could you investigate them for us?"</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.c4>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.o4>No problem.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.o4>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.c5>"Much appreciated."</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.c5>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.c6>UFO mission line completed.</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.c6>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.o5>"Yes, that girl really put quite a bit of pressure on us."</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.o5>
    <EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.c7>"You’ve worked hard." The girl bows slightly in gratitude. "We’ve already received word from Myouren Temple. It seems Nue was under the influence of some kind of wave interference and lost consciousness for a while."</EventText.touhou_akyuu_ufo_mission04.c7>

    <!--Cirno Joining Event Text-->
    <EventText.cirno_join.c1>Europa’s palette is mostly dim and gray; even the occasional bright color is only the harsh red of flares or the manic displays of clowns.</EventText.cirno_join.c1>
    <EventText.cirno_join.o1>Continue</EventText.cirno_join.o1>
    <EventText.cirno_join.c2>Yet now, before you, stands a bright blue presence.</EventText.cirno_join.c2>
    <EventText.cirno_join.o2>Blue hair and a pair of crystalline wings — just looking at her sends a chill through your body.</EventText.cirno_join.o2>
    <EventText.cirno_join.c3>However, she seems to be deep in thought, troubled by some big problem.</EventText.cirno_join.c3>
    <EventText.cirno_join.o3>“You look like you’re in trouble. Can I help?”</EventText.cirno_join.o3>
    <EventText.cirno_join.c4>“Trouble? That’s easy for me.” The girl’s frown instantly shifts into a confident grin. “But even the mightiest fairy runs into problems. I was trying to help a human with a small favor and got stuck on this puzzle.” She then hands you a sheet of paper.</EventText.cirno_join.c4>
    <EventText.cirno_join.o4>Examine the paper</EventText.cirno_join.o4>
    <EventText.cirno_join.c5>The paper lists unpaid bills and a few crooked lines of equations in the blank space attempting to total them — clearly a failed attempt. You suddenly understand the source of the girl’s worry.</EventText.cirno_join.c5>
    <EventText.cirno_join.o5>Help her calculate the total</EventText.cirno_join.o5>
    <EventText.cirno_join.c6>The girl takes back the paper, sees the result, and bursts into a delighted laugh: “Just as I thought — the human I picked is sharp!”</EventText.cirno_join.c6>
    <EventText.cirno_join.o6>Picked me?</EventText.cirno_join.o6>
    <EventText.cirno_join.c7>“I heard you run a capable fleet. I’ll reluctantly help manage it for you — no need to thank me; I get thanked all the time.”</EventText.cirno_join.c7>
    <EventText.cirno_join.c8>You can’t help but smile. Out of goodwill, you accept this ice fairy aboard.</EventText.cirno_join.c8>
    <EventText.cirno_join.o7>Bring her onto the submarine</EventText.cirno_join.o7>
    <EventText.cirno_join.c9>“From now on, I’ll take care of those annoying pests for you!”</EventText.cirno_join.c9>
    <EventText.cirno_join.c10>Cirno has joined the crew</EventText.cirno_join.c10>


    <!--任务事件文本-->

    <!--站点任务-->
    <!--Station Missions-->
    <EventText.Touhou_Easy_Mission01.c1>“There’s been so much trouble lately... having to go out every day is exhausting...” The girl flips through the papers in her hand, glances up at you, and says, “You’re here for a commission, right? Here’s the latest list—just some simple chores.” With that, she slips a sheet into your hand.</EventText.Touhou_Easy_Mission01.c1>
    <EventText.Touhou_Normal_Mission01.c1>“I just want to lie down... I’m so tired... I want to sleep...” The girl flips through her papers, then raises her weary eyes to meet yours. “You’re here for a commission, right? This one’s new—requires an experienced captain. Think you can handle it?” She hands you a sheet of paper.</EventText.Touhou_Normal_Mission01.c1>
    <EventText.Touhou_Hard_Mission01.c1>“If only Marisa were here... It’s really hard managing everything alone...” The girl fiddles with the papers in her hands and looks at you seriously. “You’re here for a commission, right? This is the latest one. The journey will be dangerous—please be careful.” She passes you a sheet of paper.</EventText.Touhou_Hard_Mission01.c1>

    <!--Darkness of Unclear Truth-->
    <Eventtext.FindHoujuuNue.c1>A strange light emerges from the murky sea, and a massive, bizarre creature surfaces from the depths.</Eventtext.FindHoujuuNue.c1>
    <Eventtext.FindHoujuuNue.c2>Your attacks are effective—the Nue’s mind seems to regain some clarity, but it grows even more ferocious.</Eventtext.FindHoujuuNue.c2>
    <Eventtext.FindHoujuuNue.c3>A strange power rages beyond the river, driving Nue’s strength into violent frenzy.</Eventtext.FindHoujuuNue.c3>
    <Eventtext.BOSS_Fight_Completed.c1>BOSS defeated. The treasure bag has been generated aboard the main submarine.</Eventtext.BOSS_Fight_Completed.c1>

    <!--Too Late-->
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission03_Event.c1>You've spent too much time here—more enemies are breaching the outpost from all directions.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission03_Event.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission03_Event.c2>A strange scent suddenly fills the air. The bodies of those raiders begin to show disturbing changes.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission03_Event.c2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission03_Event.c3>A foul, nauseating odor spreads through the air, eroding your resistances. You won’t recover until the stench fades.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission03_Event.c3>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission03_Event.c4>The air is thick with a corrosive, putrid gas that burns your flesh—you’ll only be free once it dissipates.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission03_Event.c4>

    <!--Mending the Fence-->
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission04_Event.c1>You've spent too much time here—more enemies are breaching the outpost from all directions.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission04_Event.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission04_Event.c2>More terrifying creatures emerge from the shadows—the situation is getting complicated.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission04_Event.c2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission04_Event.c3>Several dangerous creatures suddenly rush out from the darkness. You’ll need to stay alert from here on.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission04_Event.c3>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission04_Event.c4>There are unavoidable traps hidden nearby. You feel your body rapidly weakening—it’ll take some time to recover.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission04_Event.c4>

    <!--Black Dream-->
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission05_Event.c1>You hear a piercing alarm blaring inside the structure: “Level 5 alert—black mist is spreading.”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission05_Event.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission05_Event.c2>You've spent too much time here—more enemies are breaching the outpost from all directions.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission05_Event.c2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission05_Event.c3>Something other than human seems to be stirring within the black mist. In the dead silence, you can clearly hear your own heartbeat.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission05_Event.c3>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission05_Event.c3.o1>Wait until the mist clears before continuing your exploration.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission05_Event.c3.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission05_Event.c3.o1.c1>It should be safe after a while.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission05_Event.c3.o1.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission05_Event.c3.o2>Enter the mist and see what’s really happening inside.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission05_Event.c3.o2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission05_Event.c3.o2.c1>More threats emerge from within the black fog.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission05_Event.c3.o2.c1>

    <!--Control-->
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission06_Event.c1>A bone-deep chill floods your body, as if the curse of some sorcerous draught has taken hold.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission06_Event.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission06_Event.c2>Unstable magic within this outpost is being released — the surrounding space seems liable to shift at any moment.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission06_Event.c2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission06_Event.c3>The unstable spatial magic appears to have vanished, but the toxic mist is spreading faster — it turns out the spatial wards were acting as a barrier controlling the mist’s reach.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission06_Event.c3>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission06_Event.c3.o1>Repair and correct the spatial magic lattice to suppress the mist’s spread (random awake players will immediately suffer a large spike in toxin exposure).</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission06_Event.c3.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission06_Event.c3.o1.c1>The cost is worth it.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission06_Event.c3.o1.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission06_Event.c3.o2>Ignore these minor flaws.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission06_Event.c3.o2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission06_Event.c3.o2.c1>The toxic mist will continue to spread for quite some time before it dissipates.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission06_Event.c3.o2.c1>

    <!--Purge the Cursed Outpost-->
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission07_Event.c1>Strange noises come from a corner of the outpost — something dangerous seems to have appeared.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission07_Event.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission07_Event.c2>The outpost’s emergency systems still function: an alchemical spray fills the air, mending your wounds.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission07_Event.c2>

    <!--Unexpected Encounter-->
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c1>Something appears to have been disturbed — a low, continuous rumble echoes from afar.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c2>An ancient, hollow voice enters your mind: “Are you here to seek the answer at the center as well?”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c2.o1>Who are you?</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c2.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c2.o1.c1>“Traveler, if I may call you so — come, behold the splendor of Europa’s center.”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c2.o1.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c2.o2>What kind of trick is this — is this where thieves hide their loot?</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c2.o2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c2.o2.c1>“Indeed — this is the center of Europa. Allow me to unveil its sublime view.”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c2.o2.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c2.o3>Want to see what Europa’s sky looks like? Wait until the reactor blows and you’ll find out.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c2.o3>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c2.o3.c1>You decide to ignore the voice — just blow the reactor and whatever it is will be none of your concern.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c2.o3.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c3>The maddened foes seem to have been mostly dealt with. You must destroy the reactor here and upload this outpost’s data.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission08_Event.c3>
    <!--Between a Rock and a Hard Place-->
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c1>The enemies within the outpost have already discovered your presence.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2>A whisper of unknown origin slips into your ears: “Are you here for the pilgrimage as well?”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o1>Ignore the enemy’s mental interference.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o1.c1>An unknown magical force pierces your skin and drills into your mind. “Ignorant lamb, it’s time to choose — I shall inscribe the curse upon you myself.”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o1.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o1.c1.o1>Accept the curse (a random player is cursed).</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o1.c1.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o1.c1.o2>Reject the curse (chance to avoid it, or all players become cursed).</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o1.c1.o2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o1.c1.o3>Leave it to fate (no further choice — completely random outcome).</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o1.c1.o3>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o2>I’m here to uncover the truth.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o2.c1>An unknown magical force pierces your skin and drills into your mind. “Another sacrifice for the Formless God — as courtesy, I’ll let you choose a less painful death.”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o2.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o2.c1.o1>Accept the curse (a random player is cursed).</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o2.c1.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o2.c1.o2>Reject the curse (chance to avoid it, or all players become cursed).</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o2.c1.o2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o2.c1.o3>Leave it to fate (no further choice — completely random outcome).</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c2.o2.c1.o3>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c3>“Ignorant lamb, it’s time to choose — I shall inscribe the curse upon you myself.”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c3>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c3.o1>Accept the curse (a random player is cursed).</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c3.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c3.o2>Reject the curse (chance to avoid it, or all players become cursed).</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c3.o2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c4>As the power of the curse is unleashed, that eerie presence gradually fades away. The outpost falls silent, and the curse begins to dissipate.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c4>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c5>Traps left behind by previous investigators have restrained the enemies — seize the moment!</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission09_Event.c5>

    <!--Prometheus-->
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c1>The enemies here are not desperate remnants — they’re organized and disciplined. Proceed with caution.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2>An unseen voice burrows into your mind: “This is your final warning. Do not disturb the formless ritual. There is no room for negotiation.”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o1>Weren’t you supposed to be just stragglers? Who are you really working for?</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o1.c1>“Your time is running out.”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o1.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o2>I’m merely following orders to eliminate you.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o2.c1>“Not joining us is the greatest regret of your life.”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o2.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o2.c1.o1>If your abilities are only at that level, then I see no reason to join you. Is this all the manpower you’ve got?</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o2.c1.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o2.c1.o1.c1>“My army is as vast and unwavering as my will.”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o2.c1.o1.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3>Relax, I’m merely... interested in the art of the formless.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3.c1>“If that’s so... would you become a disciple of the Formless God?”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3.c1.o1>I’ve long admired such teachings. Please, free me from the prison of flesh. (If ‘Black Dream’ has not been completed, there’s a chance to skip the mission.)</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3.c1.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3.c1.o1.c1>“Your sincerity is far from enough... pitiful.”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3.c1.o1.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3.c1.o1.c2>“Your hands are stained with the blood of my disciples... pitiful.”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3.c1.o1.c2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3.c1.o1.c3>“My influence grows ever stronger... you may go.”</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3.c1.o1.c3>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3.c1.o2>My interest is purely academic. You’ve already endangered countless lives. I’ve purged dozens like you — better surrender while you can.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3.c1.o2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3.c1.o2.c1>When one material form falls, I shall manifest in another.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c2.o3.c1.o2.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c3>The experiment is complete — my material form fades away.</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission10_Event.c3>

    <!--破坏冲动-->
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission11_Event.c1>The ritual magic in the outpost has been forcibly activated, something seems to be coming</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission11_Event.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission11_Event.c3>Their numbers are decreasing, eliminate them all at once</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission11_Event.c3>

    <!--暴雨将至-->
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission12_Event.c1>The alarm has been triggered, it seems nothing can be undone</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission12_Event.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission12_Event.c2>An unprecedented ritual magic suddenly takes effect, corrosive droplets are falling</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission12_Event.c2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission12_Event.c3>The destructive storm is approaching</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission12_Event.c3>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission12_Event.c4>The storm gradually subsides, but the alarm has already alerted nearby allied forces</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission12_Event.c4>

    <!--Alliance Deploys Infected Creature-->
    <Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission12_Event_End_Mission.c1>The Coalition's stealth submarine has dropped strange creatures onto you</Eventtext.Touhou_OutpostDestroyMission12_Event_End_Mission.c1>


    <!--卫星事件-->
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c1>自从废弃空间站在无光海原出现后，大部分河童都离开了站点，转而去废弃空间站周边建立研究设施，只剩下少部分河童经营自己的商铺。\n但面前这位似乎有着不一样的事情要做。</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2>少女似乎正沉浸在手中的设计图里，完全没注意到你的存在。</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1>还是不打扰她了。</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o2>礼貌地上前询问。</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o2.c1>“人类？”少女有些谨慎地抬头看向你，“今天不营业，明天再来吧。”</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o2.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c1.o1>“我对机械也略有研究，能让我也看看那份图纸吗”</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c1.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c1.o1.c1>“离我们这么近不怕被取走尻子玉吗。”，少女正眼看了你一眼，随后视线又落回设计图上“本来是不缺帮手的，不过她们都去鸟船遗迹附近了，要找新的零件变得很麻烦……”</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c1.o1.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c1.o1.c2>似乎是下定了某种决心，少女从口袋里拿出一小块黑色物件，似乎是某种定位器。“我们最近正在研发海底的通讯技术，但是一直没有合适的材料，如果你找到了合适的材料，用这个探测器扫描一下，把矿脉地点发回来。”</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c1.o1.c2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c1.o1.c3>少女拿着探测器简单按了几个按钮演示了一下用法，塞到了你的手里“事成之后商品给你打九五折，期待你的好消息。”，说完，又自顾自地开始研究手里的设计图了。</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c1.o1.c3>
    <!--完成任务后续-->
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c2>“这么快就找到了吗”，少女有些意外，夺过你手里的样本矿石，用放大镜仔细检查了一会儿。</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3>“虽然离理想中差了不少，不过也勉强能用上嘛。”</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o1>这些材料究竟要用到什么地方？</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o1.c1>少女抬起拿着设计图的手，一副复杂的设计方案展现在你面前。“其实也没什么大不了的，火箭计划搁置后，联盟的人没有能力继续这个项目，只好花请我们代工了。”</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o1.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o1.c2>少女收回了图纸，“虽然大部分河童都没什么兴趣，但毕竟收钱办事，就算是磨洋工也要稍微认真一点，至少有了材料，后面的工作要轻松多了。”</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o1.c2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o1.c2.o1>火箭计划？这种大工程竟然也要外包吗</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o1.c2.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o1.c2.o1.c1>“准确来说我们只负责了一部分，这种东西要做得精细也太麻烦了……”，少女拿着笔，在设计图边缘空白处写下了一个名字，送到你手里“这个人之前参与过火箭项目，后来自己退出了项目，如果能把他请回来，我就轻松多啦。”</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o1.c2.o1.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o1.c2.o1.c1.o1>你自己怎么不去？</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o1.c2.o1.c1.o1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o1.c2.o1.c1.o1.c1>“和人类交流很困难的，这样吧，以后找我买东西，我都给你打九折”</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o1.c2.o1.c1.o1.c1>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o2>找这些材料可费了我好大工夫，我现在更想要报酬</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o2>
    <Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o2.c1>“给你打九五折还不够吗，真是贪心啊……”少女在手里的设计图上写下一个名字，送到你手里，“最近的火箭计划忙得我头疼，在海底天天这么压抑更头疼了。你帮我找到这个人，这个人之前参与过火箭项目，后来自己退出了项目，如果能把他请回来，我就轻松多啦。”</Eventtext.Touhou_Kappa_Satellite_Event.c2.o1.c3.o2.c1>

</infotexts>